So, in order to cut your string or wire, you're going to need cutting utensils.
With stretchy cord, you can use scissors or wire cutters.
And you can get all these at the hardware store, by the way, or bead shop, anything like that.
The tiger tail, do not use scissors.
You will ruin your scissors.
And you can use any of these type of wire cutters for tiger tail.
It's very easy to cut with wire cutters.
Do not use scissors.
With memory wire, it's way thicker.
So you don't want to use really delicate wire cutters, because you'll put little nicks in them.
They're too delicate.
So you want to get a more heavy-duty wire cutter, because it's a lot thicker.